CONTACT

xaikiran19906@gmail.com

+971 56 432 7407

Dubai, UAE

in sai-kiran-89a87978

PORTFOLIO

www.saikir.info

Bē Saikiran19906

CREATIVE SKILLS

2D/3D Animation

2D/3D Designing

2D/3D Motion Desiging

Logo & Brand Desiging

Front-end Developer

Concept Art

Storyboarding

TECH SKILLS

Adobe Creative Cloud Suit

Blender 3.1

HTML, CSS, Jquery, Bootstrap

Cinema 4D

Figma

Wordpress

Bannersnack

Microsoft Suit

Keynote

Play Canva

SAI KIRAN

Creative Designer & Animator

With 10 years of experience as a Designer and an Animator, I have gained immense knowledge of software programs and techniques that save time.

Throughout my career, I have worked in leading advertising agencies and Tech companies, where I provided some of my finest works and managed the competitive market with quality designs that were recognized internationally.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Animator & Creative Designer

Amplify Marketing Agency, Dubai, UAE 2017 - Present

Responsibilities:

- Making concepts and directing artistic vision to create content for the products in social media by Animation, picture compositing, stop-motion, photography, videography.
- Drawing storyboards for product advertisement videos and making concept arts.
- Illustrating products and their packaging in Illustrator and designing them in 3D with impressive mockups.
- Designing Websites and Front-end developing in WordPress with additional language such as HTML, CSS.
- Designing Apps in Adobe XD and giving the best UX.
- Adding VFX and compositing and editing to the advertising video in post-production.
- Designing brand guidelines including logos and icons in particular to the companies and their style.
- Animating dynamic motion graphics in 2D and 3D for events, billboard holding, Kiosk and other digital platforms.
- Problem-solving, mentoring and training the team members for higher quality work and techniques.

Animator/UI-UX designer

Entermarkets, Dubai, UAE

2015 - 2017

Responsibilities:

- Designing Mobile Apps in Figma and checking it UI UX to make sure the app is easy to use and experience.
- Drawing storyboards for infographic videos and doing their concept arts
- Designing brand guidelines including logos and icons in particular to the companies and their style.
- Animating dynamic motion graphics in 2D and 3D front page of the websites.
- Problem-solving the issue when occurred in web development.
- Designing Websites and Front-end developing on WordPress with additional language such as HTML, CSS.

SOFT SKILLS

Creativity

Time management

Communication

Adaptability

Problem-solving

Teamwork

Mentorship

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science

Osmania University (2008- 2011)

Diploma in 2D animation, 3D Maya, VFX.

Race Animation College (2011-2012)

Animator/ Designer

MediHimalayas, Hyderabad, India 2013 - 2015

Responsibilities:

- Drawing storyboards for infographic videos and making their concept arts.
- · Animating Info graphics videos.
- Designing brand guidelines including logos and icons in particular to the companies and their style.
- Designing Mobile Apps in photoshop and checking its UI, UX to make sure the app is easy to use and experience.
- Designing Websites and Front-end developing in HTML, CSS.
- Editing stock video and animating the titles to make advertising videos.

Animator/ Video Editor

People Tech Group Inc, Hyderabad, India 2012 - 2013

Responsibilities:

- Editing stock video and animating the titles to make advertising videos.
- Drawing storyboards for infographic videos and making their concept arts.
- · Animating Info graphics videos.
- · Designing logos and icons.
- Creating 2D and 3D character designs and animating them for ads.
- Designing Websites and Front-end developing in HTML, CSS.